{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701027331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701027329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701027443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701027442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" d3d92352-9d34-4c22-a89c-e442738323ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_71"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijua kwamba hakuna kitu kibaya kingeweza kumtendekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMTENDEKEA"," userResponse":" KUMTENDEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701473187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701473185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" d3d92352-9d34-4c22-a89c-e442738323ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_71"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alijua kwamba hakuna kitu kibaya kingeweza kumtendekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701473291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701473291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" f5361126-a1b1-48af-b901-7958cea462da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701482240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701482240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" f5361126-a1b1-48af-b901-7958cea462da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701496523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701496523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" f5361126-a1b1-48af-b901-7958cea462da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701504351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701504351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" f5361126-a1b1-48af-b901-7958cea462da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_75","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701779587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701779587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" f5361126-a1b1-48af-b901-7958cea462da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_73"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701779651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701779651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" cfe35c82-ad4f-438b-bae1-0dbcff02ceac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_75"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulikuwa msimu wa baridi kali na Magozwe alisimama barabarani akiomba omba kwa watu wenye magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARANI"," userResponse":" BARABARANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701788531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701788531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" cfe35c82-ad4f-438b-bae1-0dbcff02ceac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_75"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ulikuwa msimu wa baridi kali na Magozwe alisimama barabarani akiomba omba kwa watu wenye magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701793740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701793739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" cfe35c82-ad4f-438b-bae1-0dbcff02ceac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_75"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ulikuwa msimu wa baridi kali na Magozwe alisimama barabarani akiomba omba kwa watu wenye magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701801044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701801044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" cfe35c82-ad4f-438b-bae1-0dbcff02ceac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_75"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ulikuwa msimu wa baridi kali na Magozwe alisimama barabarani akiomba omba kwa watu wenye magari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701810954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701810953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701811190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701811190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701812166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701812166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701813463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701813462"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701816416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701816416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701817271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701817270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701817597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701817596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701818847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701818846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701822432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701822432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701823428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701823427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701823687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701823686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701824649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701824649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701827550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701827549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701828584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701828584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701829067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701829066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701833650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701833648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701833761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701833760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" ec743648-2e32-4c39-87cd-0aa323d8479d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701850094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701850094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e3d85fc6-42d7-4b96-89b5-c282ee617bdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_j-u-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701852990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701852990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e3d85fc6-42d7-4b96-89b5-c282ee617bdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_v_j-u-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701857832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701857832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e3d85fc6-42d7-4b96-89b5-c282ee617bdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.118"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_v_j-u-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701867695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701867695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701868080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701868079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701868582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701868582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701868936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701868936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701869352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701869352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701869832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701869832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701870061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701870060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701873294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701873293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701873330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701873329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701874059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701874058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701874452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701874452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701874459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701874459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701874552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701874552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701879830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701879829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.119","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701887572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701887571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701893106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701893106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701899854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701899854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701907039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701907039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.119","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701917353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701917353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701922536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701922536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701927911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701927910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701932939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701932938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.119","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701939594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701939593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701945135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701945134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701951284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701951284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701958528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701958528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701965892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701965892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701973145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701973145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" e787b9b9-69a3-4ba5-875d-3ac505b402ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701982592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701982592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" aefe9a59-0510-4375-8be7-70060c9d688a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701983853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701983853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" aefe9a59-0510-4375-8be7-70060c9d688a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701983916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701983916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" aefe9a59-0510-4375-8be7-70060c9d688a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548701989806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548701989806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" aefe9a59-0510-4375-8be7-70060c9d688a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702001873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702001873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702005214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702005214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702006782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702006782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702010279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702010279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wanawake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702011847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702011847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" WALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702015336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702015336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" walimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702016962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702016961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702020304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702020303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702021876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702021875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702025247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702025247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702026835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702026834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702030731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702030731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702032331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702032331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" WAKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702036291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702036291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702037859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702037859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" WADUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702041634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702041634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADUDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702043212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702043212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" WAKIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702046985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702046985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702048568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702048566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702052741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702052741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-W.rand.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702054761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702054760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548702054895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548702054895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_213826"," gameId":" 38ba942f-d3a8-414d-9bea-8e676cf45cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-W.rand.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}